module.exports = [
    {
        "question": "The owner of a banana plantation has a camel. He wants to transport his 3000 bananas to the market, which is located after the desert. The distance between his banana plantation and the market is about 1000 kilometer. So he decided to take his camel to carry the bananas. The camel can carry at the maximum of 1000 bananas at a time, and it eats one banana for every kilometer it travels.What is the most bananas you can bring over to your destination?",
        "answer": "533",
    },
    {
        "question": "Three ants are sitting at the three corners of an equilateral triangle. Each ant starts randomly picks a direction and starts to move along the edge of the triangle. What is the probability that none of the ants collide?",
        "answer": "0.25",
    },
    {
        "question": "Four people need to cross a rickety bridge at night. Unfortunately, they have only one torch and the bridge is too dangerous to cross without one. The bridge is only strong enough to support two people at a time.Not all people take the same time to cross the bridge. Times for each person: 1 min, 2 mins, 7 mins and 10 mins. What is the shortest time needed for all four of them to cross the bridge?",
        "answer": "17",
    },
    {
        "question": "A man has two ropes of varying thickness (Those two ropes are not identical, they aren’t the same density nor the same length nor the same width). Each rope burns in 60 minutes. He actually wants to measure 45 mins.How can he measure 45 mins using only these two ropes.He can’t cut the one rope in half because the ropes are non-homogeneous and he can’t be sure how long it will burn.",
        "answer": "45",
    },
    {
        "question": "A bad king has a cellar of 1000 bottles of delightful and very expensive wine. A neighboring queen plots to kill the bad king and sends a servant to poison the wine. Fortunately (or say unfortunately) the bad king’s guards catch the servant after he has only poisoned one bottle. Alas, the guards don’t know which bottle but know that the poison is so strong that even if diluted 100,000 times it would still kill the king. Furthermore, it takes one month to have an effect. The bad king decides he will get some of the prisoners in his vast dungeons to drink the wine. Being a clever bad king he knows he needs to murder no more than 10 prisoners – believing he can fob off such a low death rate – and will still be able to drink the rest of the wine (999 bottles) at his anniversary party in 5 weeks time. Explain what is in mind of the king, how will he be able to do so ? (of course he has less then 1000 prisoners in his prisons)",
        "answer": "10",
    },
    {
        "question": "You have 100 doors in a row that are all initially closed. you make 100 passes by the doors starting with the first door every time. the first time through you visit every door and toggle the door (if the door is closed, you open it, if its open, you close it). the second time you only visit every 2nd door (door #2, #4, #6). the third time, every 3rd door (door #3, #6, #9), ec, until you only visit the 100th door. What state are the doors in after the last pass? Which are open which are closed?",
        "answer": "10",
    },
    {
        "question": "How many squares are on a chess board?",
        "answer": "204",
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 13 caves arranged in a circle. There is a thief in one of the caves. Each day the thief can move to any one of adjacent cave or can stay in same cave in which he was staying the previous day. And each day, cops are allowed to enter any two caves of their choice.What is the minimum number of days to guarantee in which cops can catch the thief?",
        "answer": "12",
    },
    {
        "question": "You are on your way to visit your Grandma, who lives at the end of the valley. It’s her anniversary, and you want to give her the cakes you’ve made. Between your house and her house, you have to cross 5 bridges, and as it goes in the land of make believe, there is a troll under every bridge! Each troll, quite rightly,insists that you pay a troll toll. Before you can cross their bridge, you have to give them half of the cakes you are carrying, but as they are kind trolls, they each give you back a single cake.How many cakes do you have to leave home with to make sure that you arrive at Grandma’s with exactly 2 cakes?",
        "answer": "2",
    },
    {
        "question": "A person dies, and he arrives at the gate to heaven. There are 3 doors in the heaven. One of the door leads to heaven, second one leads to a 1-day stay at hell and then back to the gate and the third one leads to a 2 day stay at hell and then back to the gate. Every time the person is back at the gate, the 3 doors are reshuffled. How long will it take the person to reach heaven?",
        "answer": "3",
    }
]